<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Colin Hare&#39;s Portfolio on Colin Hare&#39;s Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://cthare.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Colin Hare&#39;s Portfolio on Colin Hare&#39;s Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Colin Hare</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Raspberry Spy</title>
      <link>https://cthare.github.io/project/raspberry-spy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cthare.github.io/project/raspberry-spy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The goal for the Raspberry Spy was to expand on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://projects.raspberrypi.org/en/projects/parent-detector&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Parent Dectector&lt;/a&gt; project from the Raspberry Pi Foundation. I wanted to see if I could configure the existing project to email me a photo whenever the PIR sensor was triggered instead of just taking a video.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A majority of the project was spent on mailPi module which handles all the email of the program. The camPi module is essentially the Parent Dectector code with a slight modification to have it take a picture and then call sendmessage() from mailPi in order to send an email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The remainder of the project was spent figuring out how I could avoid leaving passwords and emails embedded in the code. I ended up using the keyring library to handle both email and passwords. I setup a quick prompt to input everything along with a function to check for if an archive had already been created.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the end I had achieved what I had set out to do with my limited knowledge at the time. While there are tons of improvements that could be made to this little pet project, I&amp;rsquo;m proud of it because it was the first that I had completed since learning to program.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wger</title>
      <link>https://cthare.github.io/project/wger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cthare.github.io/project/wger/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My minor contribution to &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/wger-project/wger&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;wger&lt;/a&gt; was my first contribution to an open source project. I found the project through the site &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.codetriage.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Code Triage&lt;/a&gt; which helps open source projects find assistance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I submitted code to fix &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/wger-project/wger/issues/241&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;issue #241 &amp;lsquo;Generate nutrition plans with generator&amp;rsquo;&lt;/a&gt; which generated dummy data to use when testing the application. The experience of being able to help someone with their project and also having their guidance along the way was simply fun. I look forward to working on other projects in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Example Talk</title>
      <link>https://cthare.github.io/talk/example-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cthare.github.io/talk/example-talk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Embed your slides or video here using &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/post/writing-markdown-latex/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;shortcodes&lt;/a&gt;. Further details can easily be added using &lt;em&gt;Markdown&lt;/em&gt; and $\rm \LaTeX$ math code.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Person Re-Identification System For Mobile Devices</title>
      <link>https://cthare.github.io/publication/person-re-identification/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cthare.github.io/publication/person-re-identification/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;More detail can easily be written here using &lt;em&gt;Markdown&lt;/em&gt; and $\rm \LaTeX$ math code.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile visual clothing search</title>
      <link>https://cthare.github.io/publication/clothing-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cthare.github.io/publication/clothing-search/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;More detail can easily be written here using &lt;em&gt;Markdown&lt;/em&gt; and $\rm \LaTeX$ math code.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
